ISAAC "YAK" LITZENBERGER

WEB DEVELOPER & DIGITAL MARKETER

i@isaacyakl.com • +1-510-925-3175

isaacyakl.com • github.com/isaacyakl • linkedin.com/in/isaacyakl

Detailed web developer with 5 years of experience designing and developing ecommerce websites and web applications seeking full or part-time front-end position. Demonstrated ability to identify and create result-driven solutions; wrote the #1 most-used Paintball trade-in web app of 2015-2016. Values teamwork, integrity, and user experience.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer & Digital Marketer

New Breed Paintball and Airsoft | 08/2020 - Present

- Programmed industry-leading, trade-in web application
- Automated structured data generation with JavaScript
- Generated average monthly revenue of \$2,000+
- Wrote industry specific blogs and reviews
- Created ecommerce SOPs for training and workflow optimization

Key Achievement: Developed website features to save \$100s/mo in third-party application subscriptions

Web Developer & Digital Marketer

YourPbFriend | 03/2014 - 08/2016

- Increased revenue 10x in 2 years by switching to the Shopify platform
- Identified key areas to successfully improve over competitors
- · Created a used gun rating system to successfully build buyer trust
- Embedded YouTube content to educate and create value for customers
- Created ecommerce SOPs for training and workflow optimization

Key Achievement: Developed the #1 most-used paintball trade-in web application of 2015-2016

SKILLS

- JavaScript / jQuery
 Git / GitHub
- NextJS / ReactJS
- HTML5
- CSS3 / SASS
- Shopify Liquid
- JSON
- PHP • Figma
- Python • REST APIs
- Bootstrap
- SEO
- Tailwind CSS
 Adobe Apps

PROJECTS

isaacyakl.com

Personal website built with NextJS and published on Vercel.

- · Experiments with relative units instead of breakpoints
- · Includes web-based resume

Remote Jackbox Player

• Increased domain authority by 33% through SEO tasks A web application to find and play Jackbox games remotely, even if you don't own any.

- Uses Twitch API to find people streaming games
- Mobile focused design with multiple viewing formats
- · Built with Tailwind CSS

bRando.is

A CSS background property randomizing script capable of transitioning between images, colors, and gradients, written in vanilla JavaScript.

- · Utilizes image preloading
- · Minified for production
- Published to NPM and CDN

Keyboard Soundboard

A web browser soundboard with preset keybinds made for one of my church's events.

- Uses JavaScript to play and stop audio elements
- Animates buttons when triggered
- · Preloads sounds

Random Owen Wowson

A Discord bot that sends various movie clips of Owen Wilson saying "Wow", written in Python.

- Makes use of the Owen Wilson Wow API
- Includes a small HTTP status server

COURSES

- React For Beginners wesbos.com
- The Web Developer Bootcamp 2022 udemy.com
- Front-End Nanodegree Grow w/ Google
- Computer Science I & II CSUSM

EDUCATION